voomga.com 2015-12-06

# Support - Voomga - Vast gaming experience

### Our Commitment To Privacy

     Welcome to Voomga, an online service operated by GameWave, Inc.(“Voomga”), which includes without limitation websites such as voomga.com and online games and applications available through social networking sites (individually and collectively, the “Site”). Your privacy is very important to us. All Voomga employees and founders make it our highest priority to keep the information that our users entrust in us safe. 

We operate under high standards for keeping your privacy safe. We operate under the following guiding principles:  
• Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology  
• Your privacy remains strictly under your control

To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and permanently at the following URL: https://www.voomga.com/privacypolicy. By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy; as such policy may be amended from time to time. This notice may be updated from time to time to reflect our continuing efforts to protect our users’ privacy. You will always be able to find the latest version posted on our website.

### The Information We Collect

     1) Voomga Applications on Partner-Operated Websites

In order to use Voomga applications on partner-operated websites (e.g., Facebook, MySpace, etc.), we may require you to 1) be a registered member of a partner site, and 2) install a Voomga application on your partner site account. If your use of a Voomga application requires installation of such application on a partner-operated website, you generally must agree to such partner site’s terms of service, which often allow application developers like Voomga to store certain information about you. The terms of service for partner-operated websites vary from partner to partner in this regard.

When you install a Voomga application on your partner site account, we may assign you a unique identifying number and a default display name, which we may retain. Your display name serves as your publicly visible identity within all websites that serve Voomga applications. By default, we may assign your display name to be your first name only.

Voomga abides by the terms of service of all partner sites. If you have any questions about your privacy, please contact service@voomga.com .

2) Voomga Applications on Voomga-Operated Websites

In order to use Voomga applications on Voomga-operated websites, you may be required to first complete a registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you may be required to give contact information such as your name and email address. We may use this information to contact you when another user interacts with your profile, or to update you with your friends’ activities in our applications.

You may have the option to provide demographic and professional information (such as education, interests, and resume) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so other users can interact with your profile. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we may ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We may automatically send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the site. Voomga may store such information for various purposes including without limitation to send emails to referrals and track the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at service@voomga.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this Privacy Policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

### Service-Related Announcements

     We may send you announcements to notify you of service related notifications and product releases and features, and to solicit your feedback and input.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you will have the option to deactivate your account. In certain circumstances, such emails from Voomga may contain links for preference management and where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further emails.

### Web Site Usage

     Like most web sites, Voomga uses cookies and web log files to track site usage of the Site. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Voomga to recognize you as a user when you return to our Site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our applications. Like the information you enter at registration or in your profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the Site.

Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the Site to improve our service, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are only tied to personally identifiable information in the event we try to identify possible fraudulent activities.

We use third-party tracking services, such as Google Analytics, that use cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. We use this service to capture usage and volume statistics to help us improve the Voomga service.

### The Way Your Information Is Visible and shared

     The primary purpose of entering data into Voomga is to build your Voomga profile. Your profile is meant to be shared with fellow fans. As a user, you have control over how much information you choose to share with other fans.

We use your personal information to:

• respond to your requests for information and newsletters,  
• provide you with access to games and services,  
• notify you of changes to your tip requests,  
• provide product support, customer services and other communications related to your transactions on our website or with our products (e.g., reminders about posting you have made, expirations of postings you have made, or updates to software you have licensed),  
• determine if you are eligible to receive certain products, services or promotions,  
• provide you with additional information that may be of interest, including marketing materials, and  
• support other everyday business purposes, such as product development, job applications, and website administration.

### Sharing of Information with Third Parties

     Other than as described below with respect to Voomga service providers, we do not generally sell, trade, rent or share your personal information with third parties without your express consent, though we may directly pass onto you information from third parties that we think may be of interest. Only when you expressly opt-in to receive communications, such as through a check-box, from selected third parties whose products or services Voomga thinks might be of interest to you, will we share your e-mail address with those parties.

### Public Display of Information

     If you participate in community features such as forums or chat, your username will be visible to the public. You may also display your name, contact info through some of these services. In addition, our chat, tips and forums allow you to communicate with members of the online community. Whenever you give out information in public areas, that information can be collected and used by people you do not know so you should not give out personal information.

### Service Providers

     We occasionally employ other companies to perform services necessary to our internal operations. For example, we may partner with other companies to fulfill an order for games, deliver promotional emails, or provide customer service. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information, and are required to use it solely as directed by us for the purpose of our requested service. These companies are obligated to maintain your personal information in confidence. We may also provide postal addresses to the U.S. Post Office or other couriers for delivery purposes.

### Purchase or Sale of Businesses

     Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”), this may change in the future. We may share some or all of your personal information with these Affiliates, in which case we will request our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the personal information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. The provisions of this paragraph will also apply if we are sold as part of bankruptcy proceedings.

### Disclosures Required By Law and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites and Others

     Please note that we may disclose any information as permitted or required by law, when we believe in good faith it is necessary for safety purposes, required for legal reporting, or to protect our legal rights or enforce our Terms of Use or any contest rules. We may also disclose information about you to our auditors or legal advisors, or in response to a subpoena.

### Aggregate Information

     We may take your personal information and make it non-personally identifiable. We do this either by combining it with information about other individuals (aggregating your information with information about other individuals), and by removing characteristics (e.g., your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you. This process is known as de-personalizing your information. We may use de-personalized information in any way and share it with third parties.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

     We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Voomga employs protected facilities, data encryption on your stored personally identifiable information, firewalls, intrusion detection, and many other security measures to protect your data. We have invested many capital and human resources into our infrastructure to secure the data of our users and will continue to make additional technology investments. If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can send an email us at service@voomga.com

### Use Of Bulletin Boards

     If you use a bulletin board or blog on our Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. We do not recommend posting personally identifiable information on such bulletin boards or blogs.

### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

     Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Site or send any information about yourself to Voomga, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to Voomga or on the Site. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that Voomga might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at service@voomga.com. We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

     1) Voomga Applications on Partner-Operated Websites

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by clicking on and editing your profile within our applications. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by making the change online or by removing our application from your partner site account.

2) Voomga Applications on Voomga-Operated Websites

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by making the change online or by contacting us through the methods indicated in the “How To Contact Us” section.

### Privacy Policy Updates

     If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here by means of a notice on our home page.

### Legal Responsibilities Disclosure

     We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Voomga.

### How To Contact Us

     We dedicate resources to helping you contact us if you have questions about your privacy and personally identifiable information. You can contact us by emailing our Customer Support service@voomga.com, or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * Service-Related Announcements
  * Web Site Usage
  * The Way Your Information Is Visible and shared
  * Sharing of Information with Third Parties
  * Public Display of Information
  * Service Providers
  * Purchase or Sale of Businesses
  * Disclosures Required By Law and Disclosures to Help Protect the Security and Safety of Our Websites and Others
  * Aggregate Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Use Of Bulletin Boards
  * Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
  * How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
  * Privacy Policy Updates
  * Legal Responsibilities Disclosure
  * How To Contact Us
